嘿 这里的人们因为错过 无耻家庭
Hey, people around here get their ass beat
而被打屁股 所以 坐下来 闭上你的嘴
for missing Shameless. So sit down, shut up,
赶紧赶上来
and catch up.
否则的话 我不在乎
Or don't. I don't give a fuck.
但是我很乐意打的你满地找牙
I'm happy to knock your fucking teeth out.
赶紧去吃药
Meds and vitals now.
-那些药是干什么用的 -抗排斥
- What are those for? - Anti-rejection.
高血压 抑郁
Hypertension. Depression.
利尿 还有很显然
Diuretic. And apparently,
我的新肝脏也不怎么舒服
that is my new liver, fucking me in the ass.
-嗷 -你在干什么
- Ow! - What are you doing?
不要打我们的女儿 不过是咬了你的乳头而已
Do not hit our daughter. It's just the nipple.
我受不了了 不要再喂母乳了
I'm done. No more breast-feeding.
我要去艾莱柏酒吧工作了
I'm going to work at the Alibi.
-你可以呆在这里 -你得管管
- You can stay here. - You've got to do something
你的女儿了 她像一个
about your daughter. She's acting like
绝望的少年
a desperate teenager.
-你在撒谎 -嗷
- You're lying! - Ow.
我再也忍受不了她和她儿子查克
I don't want her and that Chuckie thing
在我的房子里呆下去了
in my house anymore.
嘿 你给那个医生打电话了吗
Hey, did you have a chance to call that doctor?
莫妮卡有的我可没有
I don't have what Monica has.
或许是和我们母亲一样的躁郁症
It could be bipolar disease like our mom.
今晚来看我们的演出啊
Come see our show tonight, huh?
-我倒是想 但是我九点就会变成南瓜
- Wish I could. I turn into a pumpkin at 9:00.
我们稍后见 嗯哼
Maybe I'll see you later, huh?
你给了很多的小费吗 -如果他是一个音乐家
- Did he leave a good tip? - If he's a musician,
那你永远都不会知道那些小费去哪了
you never know where that tip's been.
-你们作弊 -看看谁在进行病态的运动
- You guys are cheaters! - Look who's a sore sport.
看看谁深深陷入爱河
Look who's madly in love.
我正打算要大赚一笔
I'm about to start a big clean up.
他们今天早晨把霍尔斯特德街上的阳光大楼给拆了
They knocked over Sunny Days on Halsted
很棒 我加入
- this morning. - Great, I'm in.
高价格出售你的房子
Sell your home at a premium price.
我对全人类的贡献
My contribution to mankind.
我把弗兰克的上帝之乳给你了
I give you Frank's Milk Of The Gods.
想想你的幸运 并非乌有  也曾辉煌过 往昔不在 你所言为何 你肯定的又是什么 亲朋伴你左右
Think of all the luck you got. Know that it's not for naught.You were beaming once before.But it's not like that anymore. What is this downside That you speak of?What is this feeling?You're so sure of? Round up the friends you got?
并非乌有  也曾乐于此 往昔不在 你所言为何 -这是啤酒吗  -我叫它上帝之乳
Know that they're not for naught?You were willing once before?But it's not like that anymore?What is this downside?That you speak of?What is this feeling You're so sure of?  - This is beer? - I call it Milk Of The Gods.
天啊
Man.
我觉得我拉裤兜子了
I think I just shit my pants.
很好 我会减少啤酒花的
Good to know. I'll reduce the hops.
知道吗
I'll tell you what though.
这玩意他妈太糟糕了
It's bad ass.
你会用什么买这样的东西
What would you pay for something like that?
我有一些我女儿烤的破玩意
I got some sweet 420 that my girl baked up.
-你想换吗 -好好好
- You wanna trade? - Done, done, done.
啊 天啊
Aw, man.
-看看啊 -什么
- Look at that. - What?
新的一天 而且我还活着
A new day. And I'm still alive.
生活很美好
Life is good.
嗷嗷嗷嗷嗷
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
啊嗷嗷嗷嗷
Arr-ar-ar-aroooo!
-嗷嗷嗷嗷嗷 -啊嗷嗷嗷嗷
- Cock-a-doodle-doo! - Arr-ar-ar-aroooo!
嘿 你起的真早啊
Hey. You're up early.
从今天早上开始我就不再在家软禁了
I'm off house arrest as of this morning.
-哈 -而我就需要一个螺丝刀
- Ah. - And I just need a screwdriver
把这个东西弄掉
to get this thing off.
你 额 确定这样是个好主意吗
Are you, uh, sure that's a good idea?
观护所明天才会开门
Probation office isn't open until tomorrow.
只要我完好无损归还
But as long as I give it back undamaged,
那就没事 伙计 说一句
I'm good. Dude, congratulations
-恭喜你没那么难 -恭喜你 菲奥娜
- is not that hard to say. - Congratulations, Fiona.
-谢谢 -不要用
- Thank you. - Well, just try not to
自驾游或者烈性毒品来庆祝这个  行吗
celebrate with any road trips or hard drugs, yeah?
不敢保证 过好每一天
No promises. One day at a time.
你星期天就要去开始新工作了
You start your new job on a Sunday?
对啊 一些关于 额 今天城管执法不上班
Yeah, it's something to do with, uh, no city inspectors
我想他们是不是都想
working today, and I'm guessing they're planning
让我们把有毒废物倒到
on having us dump toxic waste some place where
不该倒的地方
toxic waste should not be dumped.
奇怪的是 我还有点小激动呢
Weird thing is, I'm kinda looking forward to it.
-为了倒有毒废物 -不 因为那个新工作
- To dumping toxic waste? - No, to the job.
你能想象吗 没有课 没有压力 没有成绩
You know, no class, no stress, no grades.
就在那里搬运和拆东西
Just hauling shit and breaking shit.
就像冥想一样吗 只是移动大物体
It's like meditation, only with large objects.
冥想 喔 你还真是
Meditation? Wow, you really are
-个怪胎啊 -哦 去死
a 12 step monkey, huh? - Oh, lick me.
这就是我姐
There's my sister.
嘘 嘘 嘘 嘘 嘘
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
这个 最开心宝贝 还真管用了
This "Happiest Baby" Shit totally works.
拿去 把这个也 最开心宝贝 了
Here, Happiest Baby shit this one.
嘘 嘘 嘘 嘘
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
把她放那
Put her there.
把她给我 不 放开妈咪的头发
Give me her. No, let go of mommy's hair.
这样就对了嘛
There we go, yes.
没关系的
It's okay.
因为今天是父亲节所以他们今天更爱爸爸而已
They're just loving on papa cause it's Father's Day.
好啦 好啦
Okay, okay.
嘿 话说 怎么打算的
Hey, so what's the plan anyway?
-什么打算 -煎饼
- The plan? - Pancakes?
不 华夫饼 哦 巧克力馅的烤薄饼
No, waffles? Ooh, chocolate chip pancakes.
-你在说什么 -今天是父亲节
- What are you talking about? - It's Father's Day.
-今天是父亲节 -哦妈蛋 好吧
- It's Father's Day. - Oh shit, okay.
-今天是父亲节 -对 额
- It's Father's Day. - Yeah, uh.
-今天是父亲节 -看着她
- It's Father's Day. - Watch her.
嘘 今天是父亲节
Shh. It's Father's Day.
今天是父亲节 看那个
It's Father's Day. Look at that.
看看那些技巧
Look at those skills.
凯文要该死的煎饼
Kev wants fucking pancakes.
-诶我去，你还好吗 -我生了对双胞胎
- Holy shit, you okay? - I have twins.
-我不会再好了 -去他妈的，我要上班了
- I'll never be okay again. - Shit, I gotta go to work.
好吧 额 一对宝贝的那个好运
Okay? Uh, good luck with, uh, too many babies,
卸脚环的好运 好吧
and good luck with the jailbreak, okay?
-一会见 -你干啥呢
- I'll see you later. - What are you doing?
我在解除软禁 你要咖啡吗
I'm off house arrest. Do you need coffee?
-你看起来 -看起来怎样
- You look-- - I look what?
没啥 华夫饼在冰箱里
Nothing. Toaster waffles in the freezer.
我一直盯着表数着时间
I've been watching the clock counting the minutes
直到艾莱柏开门然后盯着弗兰克用他的方法喝酒
till I can open the Alibi and watch Frank drink his way
-让酒精穿过别人的肝脏 -嗯哼 对你来说挺有意思
- through someone else's liver. - Hmm, that's fun for you,
-是吗 -这样我就是坏人了吗
- is it? - Does that make me a bad person
我宁愿卖便宜的酒
that I'd rather be selling cheap booze
给那些酒鬼也不愿意花时间和我这俩小恶魔在一起
to barflies than spend time with my twin spawns of Satan?
小恶魔 真的假的
Spawns of Satan? Really?
你觉得我是个坏妈妈吗
Do you think I'm a bad mother?
你昨晚有把你任何一个孩子扔在走廊里
Did you leave either kid on the porch
自己去买毒品吗
last night while you were going on a drug run?
所以比起我成长的经历看
Then compared to what I grew up with,
你是个无懈可击的好妈妈
you're an excellent mother.
啊 哦哈哈哈
Ah! Aahhh!
看呐看呐
What? What?
看呐 你是太 太累了
What? Are you too-- too tired
所以不陪我跳吗
to jump up and down with me?
是啊 要是管用的话 我现在脸上就挂着开心的表情了
Yeah, but if it helps, this is my happy face now.
好吧 利普 你来了 伙计
All right, Lip, you're over here, buddy.
你要做的
So here's what you're going to do,
是抬起大块的水泥
you're going to lift these large pieces of concrete,
把它们放在铲装机的翻斗里
put 'em in the bucket of the bobcat.
然后翻斗满了的时候
Then you go get some more while the bobcat
再把水泥都倒掉
dumps them in the low load.
我要开铲装机吗
I get to work the bobcat?
不是 你要先用手把这些
Okay, you're going to lift with your hands
大块的水泥抬起来然后把它们放进铲装机
the large pieces of concrete and put them in the bucket
的翻斗里像这货一样
of the bobcat just like these assholes
不说英语的都能干
who don't speak English are doing.
然后你让开
Then you're going to move out of the way
而铲装机要那些有驾驶许可证的人
while the bobcat, which has a licensed operator
是我不是你 把这些 倒掉
who is me and not you, dumps them in the low load.
然后你接着搬 这样工作八个小时
Then you're going to do it again for eight hours.
你八个小时以后就停因为我不会
You're going to stop after eight hours 'cause I'm not
支付你们加班费
paying your college ass overtime.
你觉得行吗
You think you can handle that?
应该没问题
I think I'll manage.
好的
All right.
阿曼达 啊 好胸器
Amanda, huh? Nice tatas.
把你的手机给我
Why don't you give me the phone?
-我为啥要这么做 -手机在工作现场
- Why would I do that? - Phones are a hazard
是个隐患 这样你就不能控告我
on the worksite. You're not going to sue me
支付工人的保险因为
for workman's comp because you're distracted
你被一个胸器照分散了注意力而被砖头砸伤了脑袋
by a titty shot when a brick comes flying at your head.
砖头现在向我头砸来了吗
Bricks are flying at my head now?
这不是在艾莱柏 小杂种
This ain't the Alibi, bitch.
你为我工作 你得听我的
You work for me, you do what I say.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的 动起来 动起来 哦喽喽喽喽
All right, andale, andale. Arriba, ay-yi-yi-yi.
好胸
Nice nipples.
我想给他打电话 因为他是我爸爸
And I want to call him, 'cause he's my dad,
而且今天是父亲节
and it's Father's Day.
但只是我单方面的 你懂得 这太自私了
But that's for me, you know? And it's selfish
因为他不想接我电话
'cause he doesn't want to hear from me.
而且 额 他说的很清楚
And, uh, he made that pretty clear.
额 禁令说的很清楚
Well, the restraining order made that pretty freaking clear.
所以 我不会打给他 我只会去尽力
So, I'm not going to call him, and I'm just going to work
做到最好
on me the best that I can.
真好你能来
Nice of you to stop by.
你的加糖咖啡
Here's your coffee flavored sugar.
尽我所能 是吧
All I can do, right?
你知道的 保持清醒 去工作
You know? Stay clean, go to work,
想起来的时候祈祷 所以
pray when I can remember, so...
你在用脚踝调戏我吗
Are you ankle flirting with me?
我脚踝很漂亮
I've got excellent ankles.
你现在能看到两只
Now you can see both of them.
监视器呢
No monitor?
你大周日的怎么把那个卸下来的
How'd you get that off on a Sunday?
螺丝刀 加点体力活儿
Screwdriver. A little bit of elbow grease.
-你惹麻烦了 加拉格 -嘘嘘嘘
- You're trouble, Gallagher. - Shh, shh, shh.
我试着听呢
I'm trying to listen.
这是另一个永远不会原谅我的人
And it's one more person that will never forgive me.
恶 别学他 利亚姆
Ew, don't learn from him, Liam.
-他太恶心了 -恶心
- He's disgusting. - Disgusting.
我们这个夏天怎么挣钱
What are we going to do for money this summer?
我准备能上多少雏就上多少
I plan to bang as many chicks as I can,
做的好了 她们甚至会花钱雇我做
and get so good at it, they even pay me to do it.
哈 是 对的 你都坐轮椅呢
Ha! Yeah, right. You're in a wheelchair.
-她们喜欢轮椅 -我发誓
- Chicks dig wheelchairs. - I swear to God,
你要是比我还早破处
if you lose your virginity before I do,
我就在你睡觉的时候捅死你
I'll stab you to death in your sleep.
你想让我在你三十岁的时候还是处男吗
I'm supposed to keep it in my pants till you're 30?
-30 -40
-30? -40?
-不好笑 -哈 很有趣
- That's not funny. - Yeah it is.
我一会要去公共泳池 如果你也想去的话
I'm going to the public pool later if you want to come.
你在泳池能干啥
What are you going to do
你都不能沾到水
at the pool? You can't get wet.
你忘了雏会喜欢轮椅这档子了吗
Did you miss the part where chicks dig wheelchairs?
额哼 陌生人 让我拿点防狼喷雾
Hmm, strange man. Let me get my pepper spray.
利亚姆 去开门
Liam, get the door.
你好 我 我找弗兰克 加拉格
Hello, uh, I'm looking for Frank Gallagher.
-什么事 -哦 额
- Why? - Oh, um,
他的  他的肝脏是 我
his-- his liver was my-- was--
他住在一街区远的希拉家里
He's one block over at Sheila's.
我们只是需要个能做饭的地方
We just need a place to cook
还有一个能容下三个人的餐桌
and a table big enough for three.
要是你们也想一起来参加的话  那样就最好不过了
Or if you guys want to join, that would be so wonderful.
-没门儿 -番茄酱
- No. - Ketchup.
好的 马上就来
Sure. Coming right up.
-菲奥娜  -不 不好意思 但你不能
- Fiona. - No, I'm sorry, but you're not
在我家为弗兰克做一顿父亲节大餐
cooking a Father's Day meal for Frank in my house.
六号桌是你还是我负责的
You got table six or is it me?
额 我来吧  因为弗兰克他就不像个父亲
Uh, I've got it. Because Frank is not a father.
对我来说不是 对孩子们来说不是 老实说 萨米
Not to me, not to my kids, and honestly, Sammi,
对你来说也不是  你的番茄酱
not to you either. Here you go.
-还需要点别的什么吗  -辣椒酱
- Need anything else? - Tabasco.
马上就送来
Coming right up.
-你的辣椒酱  -再来点枫糖浆
- Here you go. - More maple syrup.
马上就来  萨米 听我说
Right away. Sammi, listen to me.
弗兰克就是弗兰克 他永远不会陪在你
Frank is Frank. He'll never be there for you,
或者是你孩子的身边 他每次都会
or for your kid. He will disappoint you
让你失望的  你的枫糖浆
every time. Here you go.
再来点奶精
Creamer.
没问题  还需要其他的吗
Absolutely. Anything else?
没有啦
No.
好的
Sure.
你太冷漠了 菲奥娜  你这么年轻漂亮
You're cynical, Fiona. You're too young and pretty
不该如此冷漠无情  这让我很为你感到难过
to be so cynical and hard. I-- It makes me feel sad for you.
奶精来了 祝你父亲节快乐
Here you go. Happy Father's Day.
再来点黄油
More butter.
马上就来  萨米  听我说
Right away. Sammi, listen to me.
我并不是对弗兰克冷漠
I'm not cynical about Frank.
我只是最终变理智了
I'm just finally sane.
宝宝需要点阳光 你能带他出去走一走吗
Baby needs daylight. You take him for a run?
不能 抱歉 我得去参加个葬礼
Can't, sorry. I gotta go to a funeral.
葬礼 谁的
Funeral? For who?
-一个他都不认识的人  -他是名士兵
- Some guy he doesn't even know. - Brother in arms.
-我只需要知道这么多就够了 -他根本就没有死于战场
- That's all I need to know. - He didn't even die
好像就是一场车祸而已
in a war, man. It was like, a car accident.
去你妈的 米奇 他是为国捐躯的
Fuck you, Mickey. He died serving his country.
好吧 那我跟你一起去吧
All right. I guess I'm going with you.
-你能带着宝宝去葬礼吗 -不行 在这个国家
- Can you take baby to funeral? - No, it's illegal
那是违法的 嘿 至少你能不穿
in this country. Hey, can you at the very least
这该死的制服去吧  因为世界上的宪兵都在
not wear a fucking uniform, since every MP in the world
-找你  -他是个军人
- is looking for you? - He's a soldier.
他值得我们该死的尊重
He deserves our goddamn respect.
从现在起让我来告诉你 将会是怎样 你最好
Let me tell you from now on How it's going to be
-她还是不理你吗  -我也不理她
You had better... - She still ignoring you? - Just ignore her back.
嘿 加拉格 气色不错啊
Hey, Gallagher, looking good.
你也是啊 霍莉
You too, Holly.
又没说你
Not you.
-是你 -真的吗
- You. - Really?
噢 你可怜的腿
Oh, your poor leg.
真可怜
Poor baby.
她跟你说话只是为了气我
She's just talking to you to mess with me.
让我们期望她只是给我口来耍弄你把
Let's hope she just blows me to mess with you.
啦啦啦啦啦
La la La la-la la-la la-la
打扰一下 你对我的服务有什么意见吗
Excuse me, was there a problem with your service?
因为饭费的15%以上是支付小费的标准
Because a tip of 15% or more is standard for--
你太拖沓了
You were slow.
谢谢
Thanks.
拖沓 到底是因为我拖沓
Slow? Is it that I was slow,
还是你这臃肿的身躯忍不了5分钟
or is it that your bloated metabolism can't handle
去等一个10磅重的培根
a five minute wait for the ten pounds of bacon
吞进你那胖喉咙里
you shoved down your fat throat?
哇 哇 噢  嘿 嘿 够了 够了
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey! Enough, enough!
需要我叫警察吗 怎么回事
Do I have to call the cops? What's wrong?
-到底发生了什么事 -没给小费
- What's going on? - No tip.
我要跟你的经理谈
I want to talk to your manager.
-我就是经理 -你想怎么
- You're talking to him. - What do you plan
-处理这事  -先生 拜托
- to do about this? - Sir, please.
她在父亲节侮辱我的丈夫
She disrespected my husband on Father's Day.
-好了 女士 -她拖沓 没礼貌 而且
- Okay, ma'am. Ma'am. - Slow, rude, and my eggs
-我的鸡蛋都没熟 -先生 不冒犯地讲
- were undercooked. - Sir, respectfully,
如果你付不起小费 你就最好不要在这里吃
if you can't afford to tip, you can't afford to eat here.
你没搞错吧 你居然偏袒这个
Seriously? You're siding with this
小婊子
little slut?
放开他 放开他
Let him go! Let him go!
好 好 肖恩 放开他吧
Okay, okay. Sean, let him go.
好吧 我会放开你
Okay, I'll let you go.
但首先 你得跟我的服务员道歉
But first, you apologize to my waitress.
然后你离开而且永远不要再回到
Then you walk away and you never walk down
这条街上 你明白了吗
this street again. You got it?
明白了
Yes, sir.
对不起
Sorry.
你没事吧
You okay?
你嘴唇流血了
Your lip's bleeding.
我会冰敷一下的
I'll ice it.
嗯 猴舌 来拍进去 当帽子回荡脑海 虔诚的人不会停止 当你发誓再也不会
Well, monkey tongue, Come slap it in，As your hat pounds in your head And the religious won't stop As you swear no never again
-仅剩躯壳 拽你穿过床间  -不好意思 该死 不好意思
So you muscle all you got left. And drag your ass across the bed. Try like hell to delight.That little horse inside your head. Sorry. Shit, sorry.
我 我 我不是在看你的奶子
I-I-I wasn't looking at you-- your boobs.
或者是看那边 实际上我是在看
Or-- or-- or that way. Well, actually I'm looking...
你的奶子的  很不错
at your boobs that way. They're good boobs.
我只是
I'm just--
只是希望我的宝宝们能有奶子可吃
I just wish my babies had boobs.
该死 不好意思
Shit. Sorry.
嘘 嘘 嘘
Shh, shh, shh.
啊噢 啊噢
Ow, ow.
我的头发 头发 放开 放开
My hair, my hair, let go, let go.
你的女人没有母乳喂养她们吗
Your wife is not breastfeeding?
我 我只是有点搞不明白
I-I-I di-- I don't-- I just don't get it.
我的意思是 艾米只是咬了她几次而已 又能怎样呢
I mean, Amy bites her a couple of times and what?
她就不再想喂她了
She just quits the gig?
想像你正在游泳
Imagine you are swimming.
小鲨鱼不知从那冒出来
And baby shark comes out of nowhere,
用它们尖尖的牙齿戳你的卵蛋
and sinks his fucking teeth into your ball sacks.
宝宝咬乳头就是这种感觉
This is what it feels like when they bite nipple.
就像他们宣战了一样
Like they have declared war.
也可以说 如果你手里有把锤子
Like, if you have a hammer in your hand,
你就想把这小东西的脑浆锤出来
you could bash the brains out of this little shit.
就是这种感觉
This is what it feels like.
糟糕 我应该给小维道歉
Damn. I think I owe V an apology.
就算是这样 也没理由不喂母乳呀
But still, it's no reason to quit.
总有办法能让他们不要咬
There are ways to stop biting.
恩 我就是那么说的
Well, that's exactly what I said.
我老公对照顾宝宝没兴趣
My husband has no interest in baby.
他帮助别人 但是谁来帮你呢
Orange boy, he helps. But, who helps you?
小维有兴趣 只是  是啊
V has interest. It's just-- Yeah.
不 我的意思是 她工作太累了 所以
No, I mean, she works a lot, so.
两个宝宝 没有人可以求助
Two babies, no help?
把她给我
Give her to me.
真的吗
Really?
利亚姆 你把冰淇淋弄得到处都是
Liam, you're getting ice cream everywhere.
-你这么生气干嘛 -你为什么不告诉我
- Why do you get so mad? - Why don't you tell me
真相 -你冷静点
the truth? - You gotta chill.
根本不是什么事儿
It wasn't even a thing.
我没法冷静 你
I am not chilling out. You...
冷静 -天啦
Chill out. - Jesus!
你就是一贱逼
You are such a slut.
你跟所有有腿的都有一腿
You'll screw anything with legs.
贱人
Scumbag.
嘿 别理他们
Hey. Let it go.
他们就是些长了一身肥肉的混蛋
They were just fat assholes.
菲奥娜 我经营一个餐馆
I run a restaurant, Fiona.
那些肥肉混蛋是我的顾客
Fat assholes are my bread and butter.
等等 你现在对我生气了吗
Wait, are you mad at me now?
不 只是你要再进一次监狱吗
No, it's just you-- you could have gone
就因为三块钱 -你在说什么
to jail for what, three bucks? - What are you talking about?
虽然你取下了监控器
So you take off your monitor,
但你还在观察期 却当街吵架
you're still on probation. Fighting in the street?
为什么要去去瞎搅合
Why are you stirring shit?
我只是去要小费
I went out there to ask about my tip.
是你突然变得像个疯狗一样
You're the one who turned into a rabid dog.
我可没说那不性感
Not that I didn't find that sexy,
但我不会撒谎的 但是 你知道的
I'm not going to lie, but, you know,
左勾拳 右勾拳的
pot, kettle.
是你把那个疯了的我引出来的
You bring it out in me.
-所以全是我的错咯 -在那些肥肉混蛋
- So it's all my fault? - Get out there
没饿死之前 快离开那
before one of those fat assholes starves.
我认为查克只是轻微的智力迟钝
I think Chuckie's mildly retarded.
得有人告诉萨米
Someone should probably tell Sammi.
弗兰克 你猜不到发生了什么
Frank, you'll never guess what happened.
恩 不管发生了什么 希望比这些
Well, whatever it is, I hope it's more exciting
无聊的弱智艺术有意思
than this sad display of mentally disabled art.
-噢 饼干 -弗兰克 弗兰克
- Oh, cookies. - Frank, Frank.
有个房地产经纪人来了 他带来了两个
A realtor came by. And he was with two, like,
挺有气质的蕾丝边 他说要用高于
very clean lesbians. And he offered us double
市场双倍的价格买我们的房子
the market value for the house.
双倍啊 弗兰克
Double, Frank.
你没同意 是吧
You didn't accept it, did you?
没有 不过为什么不呢
No, but why not?
双倍 这显而易见
Double? It's got scam
就是骗人的 -父亲节快乐
written all over it. - Happy Father's Day.
噢 不好意思
Oh, sorry.
不好意思 萨米 真是抱歉
Sorry, Sammi. Sorry about that.
弗兰克 你能想象我们能用那笔钱干什么吗
Frank, can you imagine what we can do with that money?
我们可以去任何地方 我们可以到处去玩
We could go anywhere. We could travel anywhere,
环游世界 她再也找不到
anywhere in the whole world, and she would never be able
我们了
to find us.
她永远找不到我们
She would never find us.
上帝杀死士兵 因为美国喜欢基佬
God kills soldiers! Because America loves faggots!
主是我的领路人  我将一无所求
The Lord is my Shepherd; I shall not want.
上帝杀死士兵 因为美国喜欢基佬
God kills soldiers! Because America loves faggots!
是他让我躺在牧草上
He makes me to lie down in green pastures.
上帝杀掉士兵 因为美国喜欢基佬
God kills soldiers! Because America loves faggots!
是他带我到澄净之水畔
He leads me beside the still waters...
尽管我穿越于死亡之谷的阴影中
Yeah, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death...
-上帝杀掉士兵 -我也不会恐惧邪恶
- God kills soldiers! - I will fear no evil...
因为美国喜欢基佬
Because America loves faggots!
-因为艺术和我同在 -上帝杀掉士兵
- ...for though art with me. - God kills soldiers!
天啦 你们这些人都有什么毛病
Jesus Christ, what the fuck is wrong with you people?
伊恩 你还穿着制服呢 你是宪兵捉拿的对象啊
Ian, you are in uniform and you're wanted by MPs.
你能不要捅娄子吗 嘿 嘿
Can you not make a fucking-- Hey, hey!
-当众大吵大闹 -嘿 闭上你们的臭嘴
- That's making a scene. - Hey, shut the fuck up!
-你在做什么 -噢 你
- What are you doing? - Oh, you--
你要做什么 你要做什么
What are you doing? What are you doing?
他们还自称是教徒 我要去揍这些傻逼
They call themselves a church. I'm gonna bash their fucking
-让他们和主同在 -这是一个
- heads in with Jesus. - That's a terrible
糟糕的主意 闭嘴 -操他妈的
fucking idea... Shut up. - Motherfuckers.
-你还好吗 伙计 -操你妈
- Are you okay, son? - Fuck you!
你还穿着制服呢 还用个十字架
You can't wear the uniform and wield a cross
-当武器  -哦 那我是个麻烦 是吗
as a weapon, soldier. - Oh, I'm the problem, huh?
我就是那个操蛋的麻烦
I'm the fucking problem?
你在保护这些混蛋
You're protecting these assholes!
听我说
Listen to me.
我也很烦他们 但是你得冷静下来
I hate these pricks too, but you need to settle down
否则我就叫你的指挥官了
or I'll have to call your commanding officer.
-是加拉格 对吧 -不 别这样
- It's Gallagher, is it? - No, we-- we're good.
没事了 谢谢
We're good. Thank you.
我会让他冷静下来的
I got him. I got him.
停下来 如果你想搞死他们
Stop. You want to fuck them up
我们至少要有个计划
then we need a plan.
只要我们有了计划 我们就能事半功倍
We can do more damage if we have a plan.
我们回家就开始制定计划
Let's go home and make one.
上帝不要士兵 因为美国人只爱基佬
God kills soldiers! Because America loves faggots!
我们走 走吧
Let's go. Go.
他们会预先交些钱吗 比如定金
They offer any money up front? Cash today?
不会 而且她们还有专业的经纪人
No. And-- and they had a realtor.
他有名片 而且证件齐全
And he had business cards and everything.
那不合常理啊
Doesn't make sense.
也没法找到她们
Doesn't track.
嘿 萨米
Hey, Sammi!
不 弗兰克 过来
No, Frank, no. Come on.
别把她扯进来
Don't get her involved in this.
放宽心 她对钱这类事情
Oh, calm down. She's got a good head
-很在行的  -哦 老天
- for cons. - Oh, God!
-怎么了 老爸  -为什么两个女同性恋
- Yeah, pop? - Why would two dykes
会花两倍的市价来买一堆垃圾
offer double market value for this dump?
-到底有什么问题  -根本没问题
- What's the scam? - Not a scam.
这是投资 论坛报评论这个社区
An investment. Tribune named this neighborhood
有升值的可能 现在艾莱柏里所有的人
an up and comer. Alls anybody's talking about
都在谈论这个
down at the Alibi.
-老天爷啊  -怎么了
- Oh, mother of God. - What?
你绝对不能卖了它
You are not selling.
嘿 谁说要卖掉这里
Hey, who was talking about sell--
-你要卖了它吗  -弗兰克
- Are you going to sell this-- - Frank.
也许她们有女性的第二性征 但她们完全就跟
They may have female genitalia, but those lesbians
那些侵略者没什么两样
are the man moving in on our territory.
-简直好极了  -就像这样
- Oh, great. - It used to be that a--
穷人们在距市中心不远的地方
that poor folks could get a-a decent apartment
买了一个还不错的公寓 突然间 它向南
right near downtown. And then suddenly, it's moved
移动了四十个街区 接着又移动了八十个街区
40 blocks south. And then 80 blocks.
-什么时候会是终点  -好吧 也许
- Where does it end? - Well, maybe it ends
会以我们两个坐在房车里游览这个国家为终点
with you and me in an RV seeing the country.
这就像他们对待犹太人那样
This is just like with the Jews.
十年以来 他们一直声称 这样的事情绝对不会发生
Ten years from now, they'll claim it "Never happened,"
但它还是发生了 他们想让能付得起税的人
but it is happening. They want to move people in
搬进来 所以他们要赶我们走
who can pay taxes. So they push us out.
最终 我们只能流落街头
And eventually, we end up in a camp somewhere
-永远处于主流文明的边缘  -哦
- at the edge of civilization. - Oh.
一个建立在垃圾填埋场和有毒废弃物处理厂之上的流动城市
A tent city built on old landfills and toxic waste sites.
接着我们会染上天花
And then they start passing out the smallpox blankets.
哦 弗兰克 我是说
Oh, Frank, I mean--
也许就是那对女同性恋
Maybe that's the lesbians
-她们可能会出更多的钱  -好吧
- with more money. - Okay.
也许是来和女同性恋竞争的人
Or maybe it's competing lesbians.
-等等 你等一下  -不不 不 弗兰克
- Wait, would you wait? - No, no, no, Frank.
你就不能等一下吗
Would you wait a second?
你好
Oh, hello.
你好 我 我叫韦德 谢尔顿
Hello. I-I-- My name is Wade Shelton.
我是来找弗兰克 加拉格的
I'm looking for Frank Gallagher.
他移植了我儿子的肝脏
He was the recipient of my son's liver.
-哦 快进来  -谢谢
- Oh, oh, come in. - Thank you.
-进来吧  -你不能再把肝脏要回去了
- Come in. - You can't have it back.
哦 您别介意
Oh, don't mind him.
那些药物的劲还没过去 他还有些晕呢
That medical marijuana makes him a little loopy.
你好 我是弗兰克的女儿 萨米
Hi, I'm Frank's daughter, Sammi.
-你好  -你好
- Hello. - Hi.
有什么能帮到您的 谢尔顿先生
How can we help you, Mr. Shelton?
我 我本不想来打扰你们的 但是我和我的妻子
Oh, I-I-I don't want to bother you, but my wife and I
我们想在今天下午
were going to have a little supper this afternoon
招待一下我们儿子的器官接受者
for all our son's organ recipients,
-一个小小的庆祝  -多好的主意
- a little celebration. - What a wonderful idea.
谢谢 我的本意是
Thank you. Yeah, my way of...
想和我儿子过最后一个父亲节
having one last Father's Day with my boy.
很抱歉这么晚才通知您
And I'm so sorry for the late notice.
我真的很抱歉 但是我真的找了您很久
I-I really am, but well, we had a little trouble
我知道这有点奇怪
tracking you down. I know this may seem odd,
但向您这样的器官接受者 是我们对儿子仅存的念想
but you organ recipients, you're all that we have left
所以能否请您 你们两个
of our son, so would you. Both of you--
-您是加拉格夫人吗  -是的 我是
- Are-- are you Mrs. Gallagher? - I am, yes.
-我是加里格夫人  -太好了 你们
- I am Mrs. Gallagher. - Great, would you--
你们能在下午五点过来吗
would you please come at 5:00?
-有什么吃的  -牛肋排
- What are you serving? - Prime rib.
-这是我儿子的最爱  -有奶油山葵吗
- My boy's favorite. - Creamed horseradish?
-当然有  -我们会去的
- Of course, yeah. - We will be there, good sir.
太好了 太好了 谢谢 谢谢
Oh, great, great. Thank you, thank you.
-不客气 您这边走  -事实上 我非常愿意来
- Sure, let me see you out. - I would love to come actually.
只有我们两个 我不认为你被邀请了
Both of you. I don't think you're invited.
啊呀 疼 别碰我
Ow, ow, ow, stop it.
没人碰你
No one's touching you.
够了
Enough.
该你们照顾利亚姆了 别让他淹死了
Your turn to hang with Liam. Don't let him drown.
嗨
Hi.
你没事吧
You okay?
你迷路了吗
Are you lost?
嘿
Hey.
你是不是丢了个孩子
I think you lost one.
什么
What?
二 三
Two, three.
我所有的孩子都在这儿
I got all my kids.
-嘿 威尔  -老爸
- Hey, Will. - Dad!
嘿
Hey.
他是个好爸爸
He's a good dad.
想你的孩子了 是吗
Miss your kid, huh?
好像我的全身都在燃烧
Like a burn all over my body.
上菜啦
Order's up.
波士顿奶油和和爪哇红茶
Boston creme and Java black.
-我们就这么深不可测吗  -看起来昨晚
- Are we that predictable? - Looked like another
-又像是宿醉的一天  -你能记住所有
- hangover day. - Do you you remember the orders
你最爱顾客们的常用订单吗
of all of your favorite customers?
只记住了你们几个未来摇滚之星的
Just the future rock stars.
呦 你今天没带电子脚铐
Oh, you got no ankle monitor.
是啊 终于自由了
Yeah, free at last.
这样的话你今晚就没有什么借口再错过我们的演出了吧
Oh, so you have no excuse to miss our show tonight.
-哥们 我们是来这里吃饭的  -嗯？
- Dude, we eat here. - So?
所以在这儿就别表现得像只狗似的行吗
So don't act like a dog in here.
请随便无视他
Feel free to ignore him.
他存在感可挺强的
He's kinda hard to ignore.
-哥们 我们真是来这里吃饭的  -可我没办法克制啊
- Dude, we eat here. - 'Cause I-I can't help myself.
你知道 我认为 认为她可能成为我的洋子
You know, I think-- I think she might be my Yoko.
所以你这是要把我列在你的观众名单上吗
So you're going to put me on a list?
是啊 来看看怎样
Yeah. Check it out, hmm.
对了 你也可以带上你男人
Oh, you can bring your man too.
-挺酷炫的嘛  -他不是我男人
- That's cool. - He's not my man.
老板而已
Just my boss.
所以你这是笃信
So you do believe
放任他们大声喊叫这招管用
in letting them cry it out?
笃信 不 我认为那是虐待儿童
Believe? No, I think it's child abuse.
但我认为有时候只是看你怎么称呼它
But sometimes I think it's, how you call it?
无可避免之灾祸 像是用热蜡除逼毛一样
"Necessary evil." Like waxing pussy.
对 我非常同意你说的
Yeah, I totally agree with you.
尤其面对这两个熊孩子 有时候就像  草泥马
Especially with two. Sometimes it's like, fuck!
是的 那场面让人脑补无能
Yeah, I cannot imagine having two.
现在说也没用了 你马上就能体会到有俩孩子的滋味了
What are you talking about? You're about to have two.
不 这只是代孕 我把自己的子宫像青年招待所一样出租了出去
No, a surrogate. I rent uterus like youth hostel.
这酸爽 是啊说起来
That's cool. Yeah, my mom-in-law
我丈母娘为了我们也做了同样的事
did something like that for us.
只不过她要养小孩 这点我无法接受
Except she kept the baby, which is kinda wrong.
-你可别重蹈覆辙  -不会 我只是为了钱
- Don't do that. - No, I get money.
一半开始 一半分娩
Half to start, half to deliver.
我将要分娩
I will deliver.
你知道 和你闲逛 谈论这些婴儿话题
You know, this is cool. Hanging out with you,
这让我感觉倍儿爽
talking about all this baby stuff.
首先 来 宝贝
You know, at first-- Come here, honey.
跟你说真的
To be honest with you,
我一直以为你和那些提供手淫的婊子一样
I always thought you were just some handjob whore.
没事 其实我之前也一直以为
Oh, it's okay. I thought you were
你是在酒吧当个酒保没什么文化的男妓呢
illiterate bartender pimp.
呵呵 嗷嗷嗷嗷 我的头发
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow. Ow.
我觉得 你需要理发了
You know, you need haircut.
我也这么觉得 可是小维喜欢长发
Yeah, I know. But V likes it long.
进来吧
Come in.
你好呀小黛 知道斯维特拉娜么
Hey Debs. Do you know Svetlana?
当然 她是我哥哥的爱人的替代妈妈
Of course, she's my brother's lover's baby mama.
没错 你来干啥
Right. What do you want?
游泳池里有只死老鼠 你能帮我处理了么
There's a rat in the pool. Can you fish it out?
在余下的夏日里 我对公共泳池感到绝望了
I am done with the public pool for the rest of the summer.
当然没问题 你能帮我照看一会儿艾米和吉玛么
Sure, no problem. But can you watch Amy and Gemma
干脆游一次泳好了
for a while? A swim sounds nice.
为什么你对公共泳池感到绝望
Why you done with public pool?
难不成有人在里面拉屎吗
Someone shit in it?
不是
No.
那是有人惹到你了吗
Someone shit on you?
稍稍有一点吧
Sort of.
你能教我如何起作用吗
Can you teach me how it all works?
什么起什么作用
How what works?
如何让男人们对我如饥似渴
How you make guys want you,
他们什么时候会那样做 那时候我又该做些什么
and when they do, what do you actually do?
我的意思是 我虽然看过黄片 但我没怎么看懂
I mean, I've seen porn, but I'm not sure I understand
那些技术性细节 你是这方面的专家
all the technicalities. And you're a professional,
所以我觉得你应该是为我解疑的最佳人选
so I figure you're the best person to ask.
也请不要以觉得我是个智障或者孩子的口气来职责我
And please don't accuse me of being retarded or a child,
因为我我已经准备好了
because I'm neither.
我们可以去看凯伦 还有乔迪
We could see Karen. And Jody.
我们可以去看总统山
We could see Mount Rushmore.
我们可以去新墨西哥
We could go see where the-- where the aliens landed
看外星人着陆的地方
in New Mexico.
额 或者 或者我们去看火人节
Or-- or-- or we could see The Burning Man.
火人节 弗兰克 最重要的是 弗兰克
The Burning Man, Frank. And mostly, Frank,
这样我们就能摆脱萨米
we could get away from Sammi.
求你了 弗兰克 真求你了 不要在这方面和我争执了好吗
Please, Frank, please. Please don't fight me on this.
她挖掘了我内在的某种机能
Because she just brings something out in me.
我之前并不清楚那是什么
I don't fully understand it.
现在我知道了
It's hate.
那是厌恶
我真心厌恶她
I hate her.
弗兰克 我真心厌恶你的女儿
I hate your daughter, Frank.
我宁愿卖掉这座我心爱的房子
And I'm willing to sell this house that I love
-只要能摆脱她  -希拉 我懂了
- to get away from her. - Shiels, I get it.
我真的明白你的心情
- Yeah. - I-I-I get it.
萨米是那个不知道如何去爱的倔强犊子
Sammi is a tough nut to learn to love.
和你说句实话吧 我直到今天都不明白应该
And if we're being honest, I have heretofore failed
如何与她相处
on that front myself.
但我绝不会掺和到这件
But I will not participate in the destruction
-事情中来的 -哦
- of my neighborhood. - Oh!
不 我将在留在这里
No, I will be remain here on the South Side
在芝加哥南部酿我的啤酒
of Chicago, and launch my beer,
我相信这个文化遗产要比火人节
which will be a far greater legacy
什么的要高大上得多
than any "Burning Man" Will ever be.
可是我想去看火人节
I want to see The Burning Man!
老娘就是想去看火人节
这我就不懂了 他都烧着了怎么还能活着
I don't get it. Is he alive and burning?
难不成他每天自燃一小点 健康生活一辈子
Does he burn himself a little bit each day?
我怎么知道他是怎么 怎么燃烧的
I don't know! I don't know how he burns or--
我不知道 但我 我就是想知道
I don't know. And I-I want to know.
老娘就是想知道
I want to know!
我懂你
I-I know.
嘿 发生什么事了
Hey. What's going on?
怎么都是些没用的烂枪
I see plenty of fucking peashooters,
我们有 呃 全自动武器吗
but do we have any, uh, full automatic weapons?
手榴弹
Grenades?
好吧 没关系
Okay. All right.
- 啥    -你有能穿透盔甲的
- What? - You got any armor piercing
- 弹药吗  - 为什么问这个
- ammo? - Why?
因为我他妈的需要 这就是为什么
Because I fucking need some, that's why.
唷 你得让你的炮友讲点秩序 伙计
Yo, you need to get your bitch in line, man.
好吧 这就是我们要做的事情
Okay, here's what we're going to do.
我们要召集一些我认识的家伙
We're going to call in some guys I know.
他们都是很讨厌这类事情的老兵 就和我们一样
They're veterans who are sick of this shit, just like us.
他们会和我们一起战斗的 之后呢 我们将会
They'll fight with us. And then, we'll burn down
烧掉那一整座该死的教堂
that whole fucking church with all the
让里面所有恐同者和它一起送葬
homophobic trash inside.
- 他看上去疯了  -你这么觉得吗
- He's freaking out. - You think?
-操  -他嗑了什么药吗
- Fuck. - Is he on something?
这他妈倒好了
I fucking wish.
我们该怎么办 给菲奥娜打电话吗
What do we do? Call Fiona?
你觉得菲欧娜可以阻止他对着一群
Think Fiona can stop him from going postal
-基督真爱粉发飙吗  -呃 我觉得他病了
- on a bunch of churchgoers? - Well, I think he's sick
- 她以前处理过这种状况  -她会把他送到
- and she's dealt with it before. - She'll send him
一个该死的心理医生那儿去的 不
to a fucking shrink. No.
我们自己解决
We fix this ourselves.
唷 大兵瑞恩 我有个计划
Yo, Private Ryan. I got a plan.
今天就到这里 伙伴们  多谢了
That's the day, guys, thanks!
加拉格尔 你还是站着呢
Gallagher, you're still upright.
- 是啊  -没想到你还挺行嘛
- Yeah. - Didn't see that coming.
嘿 是谁让他整天做那个的
Hey, who had him making it the whole day?
-不是我  -也不是我
- Not me. - No chance.
-所以得到的钱归我喽  -不 想啥的
- So the pool's mine? - No, fuck that.
这些钱够我们去艾莱柏喝一轮的了
The pool buys us all a round at the Alibi.
是啊 如果我是你的话 我就在那个电话上放一些漂白剂
Yeah, I'd get some bleach on that phone if I was you.
他把它在马桶里放了一小时
He had it in the port-a-john for an hour.
闭上你的臭嘴 沙利文
Shut the fuck up, Sullivan.
嘿 我们去冲个澡
Hey, we hit the showers,
之后我们就去酒吧 大学生
and then we go to the bar, College.
除非你觉得凭你的身份不屑于和我们一起喝酒
Unless you think you're too good to drink with all of us.
不 我一会儿和你们在那里见 好吗
No, I'll see you guys there, all right?
-好吧  -好吧
- All right. - All right.
好吧 现在他妈的都给我出去
All right, get the fuck out of here.
嘿 爹地 我准备好了
Hey, dad. I'm ready.
看在上帝的份上 萨米 有点自尊心好不好
For God's sake, Sammi, have some pride.
没人邀请你去参加这个晚宴
You're not invited to this dinner.
希拉 今天可是他妈的父亲节
Sheila, it's fucking Father's Day
- 而我就是他该死的女儿  -咳 咳 咳 行了
- and I'm his goddamn daughter. - Whoa, whoa, whoa, Nellie.
塞拉 萨米 让我们把这当成一次彻底的家庭行动吧
Sheila, Sammi, let's make this a whole family event.
-哦  -嘿 我肯定那里有很多
- Oh. - Hey, I'm sure there's plenty
大排骨在等着我们
of prime rib to go around.
你快去把查克也接出来吧
Why don't you run in and get Chuckie?
谢谢你 爸爸
Thank you, daddy.
太感谢了  查克
Thank you. Chuckie!
- 快出来 宝贝  -她没有被邀请
- Come on, baby! - She wasn't invited.
-等等  -我们要和爷爷一起出去
- Wait. - We're going out with grampa.
- 快跑 -啥
- Run. - What?
- 快跑 就现在  -哦
- Run. Now. - Oh.
利普
Lip?
- 嘿  -你衣服都湿了
- Hey. - You're soaking wet.
是啊 呃 啊 降温嘛(两个词均有性意味)
Yeah, well, uh, wet beats hot.
你这是在调戏我吗
That a come on?
-你看起来 呃  -像一个教堂女孩儿吗
- You look, um-- - Like a church girl?
- 是啊  - 哦 很好 那才是重点
- Yeah. - Oh, good, that's the point.
伊恩怎样
How's Ian doing?
不太好 但我们没事了
Not great. But we have it covered.
至少 今天没事了
I think... at least today.
如果要我帮忙尽管 对我
Well, let me know if I can, uh--
嗯啊 我会的
Yeah, I will.
嘿 你 啊 你有女朋友了吗
Hey, you, uh, you got a girlfriend?
呃 我 我这个夏天都在这里 如果你想
Well, I-- I'm around, this summer, if you wanna--
只是 只是别打电话 因为肯雅塔 你懂的
Just-- just don't call 'cause Kenyetta, you know.
-好吧  -有空来看我
- Right. - Come by my work
-如果你想的话  -好吧
- if you want to hang. - Okay.
你看起来真漂亮 曼迪
You look really pretty, Mandy.
我会与你相见  会在门口与你相见 我们在
I'll meet you By the facts, your door I'll meet you Where
那家公司倒下的地方相见 是啊 现在把球传过来 保佑你 它已经热起来了 嘿
the company falls And yeah pass the ball Bless you now, it's been warm Hey.
我们走吧
Here we go.
好吧 宝贝
Okay, baby.
像我们说的那样做
Do like we talked about.
我给你一些私密空间
I'll give you some privacy.
真的把他们的头固定下来 哦 漂亮宝贝
Really got their head screwed on Oh pretty baby,
会把他们逼疯的  -打扰了 我 我真的需要和那位牧师谈谈
gonna drive 'em crazy Excuse me, I-I really need to talk to the Pastor,
- 他在这儿吗  -举起你的胳膊
- is he around? - Hold up your arms.
-对不起  -得检查下你有没有武器
- Sorry? - Gotta check you for weapons.
因为我无法更好解决 能帮帮我吗
cause I can't settle for more?I could get sent away ?
子弹发射 子弹发射 嗨
Bullet sent away Bullet sent away Hi.
NA会员可没有会费和其他收费
There are no dues or fees for NA membership.
我们是靠自己捐款自营的
We are self-supporting through our own contributions.
NA没有与任何部门 教派和政治势力结盟
NA is not allied with any sect, denomination, politics--
- 我就说我会在这里遇到你
- I thought I might find you here.
一天里两场互助会吗
Two meetings in one day?
但今早的互助会可没有让我
Well, I didn't get that much
学到多少东西
out of this morning's meeting.
因为我坐在我喜欢的人旁边
'Cause I was sitting next to this guy I really like.
你想今晚和我去看一个乐队演出吗
You want to go see a band with me tonight?
是的 我在邀请你和我约会
That was me asking you on a date.
好啊
Yeah.
因为我看出来你可能不会邀请我出去
'Cause I figure you kinda can't ask me out,
你知道 因为我为你工作
you know, 'cause I work for you.
而且你知道 上一次我跟我老板约会的结果
And you know how well it went for me
有些令人失望 不过
last time I dated my boss, but...
我把电子脚铐给取下来了
I got my ankle monitor off, and...
这样就比较没问题了
it feels like progress.
我不知道 我想 管他呢
I don't know. I thought, "What the hell?"
所以
So...
我现在邀请你
I'm asking.
你要答应吗
Are you gonna answer?
散会后我再答复你行吗
Can I answer after the meeting?
这次会上没有串读环节
There's no crosstalk at this meeting.
谁想要先开始
Who would like to start reading?
那个疤很不错 很漂亮
That's a good one there. Beautiful.
跟你说了 很不错吧
I'm telling you, isn't that something?
-你那个更好看 -看这些
- That's a better one. - These are.
我敢打赌那些婊子们肯定喜欢
I bet the chicks love that.
-你能让它动起来吗 -哇
- And you can make it move. - Oh.
好吧 有趣的故事 以前真是一团乱
Okay, interesting story. This was a screw-up.
她感到有些疼痛 然后 哦 肾就烂了
She got some pain and just-- oh, my kidney.
我要 我要再 我要再次感谢你们
Again, I'd li-- I'd like to-- I'd like to thank you
的到来 呃 我真希望你们
all for coming. Uh, I really wish that...
能有机会见过大卫
you all could have met David.
他生性勇敢 死得也勇敢
He died bravely, the way he lived.
他与一个入室窃贼殊死搏斗
He was fighting off a home invader.
真希望我曾经教过他要逃跑
I really wish that I'd taught him to run
-而不是搏斗 -那确实 不是吗
- instead of fight. - That's true, right?
-韦德 -晚餐准备上桌了
-Wade. -Dinner's about ready.
这就是她 这就是她 各位
Here she is. Here she is, everyone.
这是我的妻子 大卫的母亲 劳拉
This is my wife, and David's mother, Laura.
劳拉 他们是
Laura, this is...
大卫
David.
大家好 感谢你们的到来
Hello, everyone. Thank you for being here.
对我丈夫来说 你们的到来很重要
It means a lot. To my husband.
劳拉 我是弗兰克 我得到的是大卫的肝脏
Laura, I'm-- I'm Frank. I'm the liver.
噢 是的 我是希拉
Oh, yeah, and I'm-- I'm Sheila.
-我是弗兰克的妻子 -我是哈罗德 我得到了肺
- I'm Frank's wife. - I'm Harold, the lungs.
你好 我是爱丽丝 我得到了眼角膜
Hi, I'm Alice. I'm the corneas.
你们好
Hello.
-我操 -嗨 大家好
- Oh, fuck! - Hi, everyone.
我是弗兰克的女儿 萨米
I'm Frank's daughter, Sammi,
这是他的孙儿 查克
and this is his grandson, Chuckie.
如果我们来迟了我很抱歉
I am so sorry if we're late.
查克要非去拉屎 真烦
Chuckie had to go number two real bad,
所以我们耽搁了一些时间
so, we lost a little time.
我妈妈心都碎了
My mother's heartbroken.
我爸他 又开始喝酒了
My father, he started drinking again.
然后是我哥 他根本不听劝
And my brother, he won't listen to reason.
他为什么选择了当基佬 而不要家庭
Why would he choose faggotry over his family?
为什么
Why?
这是种毁灭之罪 曼迪
It's a sin that destroys, Mandy.
你要把这种罪孽与你的生活彻底切断
And you have to cut that sinner out of your life.
我有差不多三十天没吸了
I'm just under 30 days clean.
但我仍然每天都很想吸
And I still think about using every day.
因为它是永恒的诱惑
Because it's a constant temptation.
就像在对我叫喊
Like a yearning.
我感受到它在肌肤脾胃中的流动
I feel it in my stomach and my skin.
不 不 不 算了吧
No, no, no. Forget it.
放屁吧你
Bullshit, man!
-那不是我的主意 -操你祖宗 我不管
- It was not my idea. - Fuck that, I don't care.
上吧 这是唯一的办法了
Come on. It's the only way to do it.
-总得有人做 -没门
- Somebody's got to do it. - No way.
-肯定有别的法子 -谁要去做
- There's another way. - Who's doing it?
-我不干 -我来吧
- Not me. - I'll do it.
不 你会用力过猛然后杀了那个狗娘养的
No, you'll go overboard and kill a son of a bitch,
-你自己心里清楚 -好吧
- and you know it. - All right.
那你来 这是你的主意
You do it. It's your idea.
这正是为什么我不用亲自去做
That's exactly why I don't have to do it.
-因为这是我的主意 -听着 听着
- It's my idea. - Listen, listen--
-我可以把他那妈个巴子的头盖骨敲碎
- I'll crush his fucking skull,
但是不 我不干这票 太操蛋了
but no, I'm not playing this. It's too fucked up.
操 伊恩说得对 那个狗娘养的
Fuck that, Ian's right. The son of a bitch
确实该死
deserves to die.
让我来吧 我要为国而战
I'll do it. I'll do it for my country.
为军而战 为你们所有人而战
For the army. For all of you.
让我来
I'll do it.
为了你的国家
For your country.
操他妈的 他人呢 你应该给他下药的
Where the fuck is he? You were supposed to drug him.
没必要 他已经上路了
Didn't have to. He's on his way.
好吧 让我看看你的脸
Okay. Show me your face now.
-我的脸 -你诱惑的那一面
- My face? - Your seductions face.
你没有母亲吗
You have no mother?
-嗯 算不上有 -好吧
- Uh, not really. - Okay.
噢 这是干嘛用的
Ooh, what's that for?
我妈对我做过的 我现在要对你来做
So I could do for you what my mother did for me.
我的儿子曾经是
My son was--
现在也是 我生活的中心
My son is the center of my life.
在这个令人痛苦的父亲节
It just-- it means so much to us to have you here
你们能来这儿对我们而言太有意义了
on this very painful Father's Day.
十八年来我第一次没跟我儿子一起过 所以
My first in 18 years without my boy, so--
真的好巧啊
That is such a coincidence.
这也是我过的第一个有父亲在的父亲节
Because this is my first Father's Day ever with a dad.
呃 好吧
Well... okay.
肉真好吃 劳拉
Great meat, Laura.
-干杯 -不
- Cheers. - No.
不 不 不好意思 等 等一下
I-I-I-I'm sorry, but ex-- excuse me.
你 你不应该喝酒
You-- you are not supposed to drink
你做了肝移植手术
when you have a donor liver.
正好相反 我做了大量调查研究
On the contrary, I've done extensive research,
如果我按照正常的节奏生活
and this liver will last me close to a decade
这个肝能让我活上快十年
if I pace myself correctly.
对 管他的 有人有烟吗
Well, fuck it. Anybody got a smoke?
天惹
Oh, God.
老鼠没了 加入了液氯 泳池好得就像
Rat's gone, chlorine's in, pool is as good as--
-我操 -噢 他是个男的
- Holy shit. - Oh, he is man.
快使出你诱惑的一面
You try seductions face.
我操你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
快把你的舌头收进去
Put your tongue back in your mouth.
这他妈是在干啥
What is this shit?
五分钟前你还是个乖宝宝呢
Five minutes ago you were a baby.
但是她看起来真的很棒 对吧
Well, she looks good, yes?
啊 我是不会评论的
Ah, I'm not answering that.
- 我就当这是承认了 - 菲奥娜会疯掉的
- But, this means yes. - You know, Fiona's gonna flip.
我不再是个孩子了 请接受这点
I'm not a baby anymore, Kev. Deal.
我不能 你能把那玩意儿放下吗
I can't would you put that down?
而且为啥这上面套了只安全套
Why is there a condom on it?
哦 你就知道说别人是吧
Oh, and what about you, huh?
你老婆怕麻烦 所以不给孩子们母乳喂养
Your wife no like pain, so she takes breasts away from babies.
你也怕麻烦 所以解决方法是把你的头发剪掉
You don't like pain, so we take hair away from babies.
得了吧 你家里到底谁在做主呢
Come on, who wears testicles in family?
是你 还是你老婆
You or wife? Huh?
是啊
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
-嘿  -哦 现在几点了
- Hey. - Oh, what time is it?
天啊 你吓到我了 你是嗑了什么药吗
Jesus, you scared me. Did you take something?
哦 是啊 还不是那个移民和罪犯泛滥的工地工作给害的
Oh, yeah, a job for illegal immigrants and convicts.
我操啊
Oh, shit.
要喝点儿酒祛祛痛苦吗
You want to drink the pain away?
我在考虑要不要去看那个乐队演出呢
I was thinking I might go see this band.
而且肖恩放了我鸽子
And Sean blew me off so--
你和肖恩到底有没有在交往啊
You and Sean, you're a thing?
我是这么以为的 但是 谁知道
I thought, maybe. But... who knows?
-你要不要去 -我不行啊
- You want to go? - I can't.
-我得去艾莱柏一趟 -去干啥
- I gotta go to the Alibi. - Why?
工作需求
It's a job requirement.
痛
Ow.
嘿 小维 在吗 想不想翘班
Hey, V, it's Fiona. Want to cut out of work
去热舞一下啊
and come dancing?
卡尔让我进来的
Carl let me in.
是我太心急了吗 吓着你了吗
Did I overstep? Freak you out?
不
No.
我只是不能
I just can't.
我很想 菲奥娜
I want to, Fiona.
但我就是不能
But I just can't.
你连陪我去看场乐队演出都不行吗
You can't come see a band with me?
不是 我 我我能与你一起做任何事
No, I-I can't anything with you.
-你太 呃    -太怎么
- You're, uh... - What?
危险了 你太危险了
Dangerous. You're dangerous.
听着 我知道你可能不是那种太擅长于
Look, I know that there's a thing like you're not
和才加入互助会的人交往 不过
supposed to date newcomers or whatever, but...
我并不能算是互助会的新人 因为我压根
I'm not really a newcomer 'cause I'm not really
就不是毒瘾患者
a drug addict, so...
我不会因为与你约会而受到伤害的
You won't be damaging me by dating me.
不 我 我会伤害我自己的 瞧 你之所以去互助会
No, I-- I'd be damaging me. See, you go to these meetings
是因为法官要求你这么做 这很好
because the judge ordered you too, and it's fun,
你还可以学到东西
and you learn a little something.
但对我来说 这些互助会 呃
But for me, those meetings, uh,
你知道的 拯救了我的人生
you know, they saved my life.
真的 每一天 都在拯救我的人生
Literally, every day. Save my life.
好的 我懂 我懂
Okay. I get it, I get it.
我不会再在互助会上与你调情了
I'll stop flirting in the meetings.
不仅仅是在互助会上 你知道吗 这就是场灾难
It's not just the meetings, you know, it's chaos.
-你到哪里 哪里就是场灾难 -但我已经在改善了
- Just chaos follows you around. - But I'm doing better.
你自己取下了监控器
You took your monitor off yourself.
-所以呢 -你应该等等的
- So?  - So you should have waited
-等警官来帮你取 -不过就是个监控器
- for the PO and you know it. - That's a technicality.
怎么 你要因此而教育我吗
You're going to judge me for that?
不 我并不想教育你
No, I'm not going to judge you for that,
我反而希望你这么做
I'm going to want you for that.
我认为你用螺丝刀取下监控器
I find it charming as fuck
这件事真是太他妈棒了
that you took a screwdriver to your monitor,
而且你午饭前因为打架而造成嘴角流血 这对我来说
and I find it sexy as hell that you had a bloody lip
-也是要命一般的性感 -你在逗我玩儿吗
- before lunch today. - Are you making fun of me?
不 我只是在说你是个混乱制造机 菲奥娜
No, it's just you're a chaos junkie, Fiona.
而我更是混乱混乱机 我爱死混乱了
And I'm a junkie junkie, so I love chaos,
但一旦我真的混乱起来 一切都会变糟
and when I get into chaos, bad shit follows.
- 而像你这样的女人 -我这样的女人
- And women like you-- - Women like me?
是啊 如此火辣 性感
Yeah. Wo-- Hot, sexy,
难以拒绝
irresistible,
有趣
fun,
喜欢制造麻烦
troublemaking,
不乱不休
chaos causing,
你这样的女人
women like you...
就是我在沉迷于海洛因之前的毒药
were my drug of choice long before I got into smack.
其实挺有趣的
It's funny, in fact.
正是有个像你一样的女人让我吸食了第一口
It was a woman just like you shot me up the first time.
-我绝不会让你这么做的 -是的我知道
- I would never do that. - No, I know.
但你会让我再次堕落的 菲奥娜
But you're a slippery slope for me, Fiona.
就因为今早上那个人没有给你小费这件事
I coulda beat that guy to death this morning
我可以把他打成半死
'cause he didn't tip you.
这当然不是你的错 完全不是
And it's not your fault. That is not on you.
是我自己的错
That's on me.
但是我 我有个儿子
But I-I have a son.
不论我有多么多么想要变坏 或者是
And I won't risk my relationship with my son
多么想和你一起做疯狂的事
no matter how badly I...
我都不能 决不能那我 和我儿子
want to do very, very bad things
之前的关系来冒险
both to and with you.
我不是场灾难
I'm not just chaos.
我已经改善了 我在改善了
I'm better. I've changed.
我觉得我真的会对你很好的
I think I could be really good for you.
我希望你继续参加这些互助会
I hope you keep coming to these meetings
因为我觉得它们真的能帮助别人
'cause I think they help everyone.
但我请求你
But I'm asking you--
我真的请求你 菲奥娜
I'm really asking you, Fiona.
下次请不要坐我旁边了
Just sit somewhere else when you do.
嘿
Hey.
哦天啊 你乳房上面那个是艾米吗
Oh, my God. Is that Amy on your tit?
但她真的很喜欢我乳房啊
Who can tell them apart?
苦了你了 宝贝 凯文
Come here, baby. Kevin!
宝贝儿 怎么了
What's up, babe?
我 我操
What? What the--
你的头发去哪儿了 这他妈什么鬼
What happened to your head? Wh-- what the fuck?
你完全不知道这样有多清爽
You have no idea how good this feels.
以后每个夏天我们都该把头发剪掉
We should shave our head every fucking summer.
啥 我 等等
What? I-- Wait.
好吧 首先
Okay. First of all,
为什么我的女儿在一个妓女的乳房上
why was there a hooker's tit in my baby's mouth?
好了好了 这个妓女可是我们认识的斯维特拉娜
All right, with the hooker. It's Svetlana.
我们的配方奶都喝光了 我总得想办法吧
And we ran out of formula, so we had to improvise.
你可以给我打电话呀 我可以买回来呀
You coulda called me. I would've brought you
或者也可以叫她出去
some formula. Or maybe she coulda went out
-买回来呀 -上帝没有创造配方奶
- and got some. - God didn't make formula,
维罗妮卡 上帝创造乳房是有原因的
Veronica. God made boobs for a reason.
嘿 发生什么事了 哦 我操 小凯
Hey. What's going-- Oh shit. Kev.
嘿 菲奥娜 嘿 小维
Hey, Fiona. Hey, V.
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
- 哦 上帝啊 -黛比
- Oh, my God. - Debbie?
- 我了个大操啊 -这是你做的吗
- What the fuck? - Did you do this?
哦我觉得 大概到了宝宝们睡觉的时候了
Know what? I think it's time for baby's nap.
是的 抱歉 那么再见吧
Okay, excuse me. Okay, bye-bye.
你头发到底怎么回事 如果是因为有虱子
What happened to your hair? If it was lice again,
-我可以给你洗掉的 -不不 是因为太热了
- I could have washed it. - No, no, it was hot.
而且孩子们总是拉扯它们
And the kids were pulling on it.
可我喜欢你的长发 那 那他妈是我的长发 凯
I loved that hair. That-- that was my hair, Kev.
你 你怎么能这么做
I-- How could you do this?
他怎么能这么做
How could he do this?
小维 不过是头发而已 会长出来的
V, it's just hair. It'll grow back.
你不仅让一个妓女来母乳喂养我们的孩子 你还把头发剪了
You fed our baby hooker's milk and you shaved your head.
好了 行了 我们走吧 行吗 我们还是出发吧
Okay, okay, let's go, okay. We're just going to go.
我们去热舞 走吧 去酒吧嗨起来
Let's go dance. Come on, let's go to the bar.
你他妈都变成啥样了
Who the fuck are you?
这他妈只是个头型而已嘛
It's just a fucking haircut.
是啊你就继续这样认为吧 好了 我们走
Keep telling yourself that. Come on, let's go.
回见 小凯
See you, Kev.
曼迪 你真是个美好的女孩
Mandy, you sweet, sweet girl.
但这样做会是罪过的
It's still a sin of the flesh.
但是上帝希望我能为你吹箫
But God wants my mouth on you.
他希望让你感受这份爱意
He wants you to feel his love through me.
闭上眼 牧师
Look away, Pastor.
我不想让你看见我做这种事
I don't want you to see me sinning.
我不想让你把我看低
I don't want you to think less of me.
但是曼迪 上帝赐予了你如此美貌
But God granted you such beauty, Mandy.
如果你不看的话
But if you don't watch,
我就可以把这看作是祈祷
then I can pretend I'm praying.
太棒了
Yes.
-射得真快啊 -什 这是什么意思
- Really fast. - What-- what is this?
-这张不错 -你们在做什么
- That's a good one. - What are you doing?
哦 发推特和脸书呢
Oh, I'm Tweeting. Facebook too.
发了
And done.
所以你要怎么对媒体解释呢 牧师
So what are you going to tell the press, Pastor?
说你以为为你口交的是一个
That you thought you were getting blown
-小女生吗 -哦
- by a teenage girl? - Oh.
-或是上帝本人呢 -哦我的天啊
- Or by God himself? - Oh, my God.
不过是个头型罢了 为什么每个人都反应这么大
It's just a haircut. Why is everyone freaking out?
不仅仅是头型 你 你看起来就像
It's not just a haircut. It's you-- you look like--
像什么 我看起来像什么
What? I look like a what?
哇 你看起来就像个妓女
Whoa, you look like a hooker.
-真的吗  -天啊
- You think? - That is not
-这不是在赞美你 黛比  -这可是卡尔说的
- a compliment, Debbie. - From Carl?
-那就是赞美 -妓女很棒
- Totally is. - Hookers are hot.
-你听 -黛比
- See? - Debbie.
你是个聪明的女孩 你都在干些什么
You're a smart girl. What are you doing
-和妓女一起玩儿  -我怎么知道
- hanging out with whores? - I don't know.
你不也挺聪明的吗 那为什么还因为吸毒
You're a smart girl. Why are you on probation
而坐过牢
for drugs?
你那两个朋友还没与你说话吗
Your friends still aren't talking to you?
什么朋友
What friends?
其实呢 你的发型
You know, your haircut
看上去确实挺不错的
actually looks pretty cute.
但你必须把你的妆都给卸掉
But you're gonna have to take that makeup down
至少得卸一半
by at least half.
好吧
Fine.
你现在打算干什么呢
What are you doing right now?
你想要和我一起去看乐队表演吗
You want to come and see a band with me?
好啊
Yeah.
你这澡洗得挺长的嘛
It was a long shower.
你是手淫去了吧
Oh, you pussied up.
这个嘛 与迈阿密的女友打了个性爱电话罢了
Yeah, well, might have been some phone sex with Miami.
你们这群人在那家前救护中心废墟上面修些什么呢
What are you guys building on top of the old nursing home?
我不修东西 我只是搬运
I don't build. I'm just demo.
我来告诉你那儿会修成什么
I'll tell you what it is.
我来告诉你们所有人
I'll tell you all what it is.
那儿要修一个星巴克
It's a Starbucks.
或者其它什么手工饮料店
Or some sort of artisanal juicery.
要不就是什么食品店
Or a whole fucking foods.
别说了 弗兰克 好吗
Just drop it, Frank, all right?
我的朋友们 我这是在说他们要把这片区域高档化呢
I'm talking about gentrification, my friends.
-高什么档 -我是在说
- Genital what? - I'm talking about
从破败处逢生 我曾经见识过
the beginning of the end. I have seen this before
64年时的富尔顿街
on Fulton Street in '64.
还有68年时的卡比街
On Kirby Street in '68.
房地产经纪人用比市场价高的价格
Realtors started buying up property at better
买下那些地 然后几个月时间内
than market value, and within a few months,
那些街区就焕然一新成为上流街区了
the whole neighborhood was over run with the gentry,
然后我们就会被赶走 如今 这些城市上流人员
and we were forced out. Today, the urban gentry
就是那些有钱的拉拉们 他们敲响你家的门
is monied lesbians. They knock on your door.
提供你两倍于你家房产的价格
They offer you twice what your home is worth,
她们之所以这么做事因为她们知道行情内幕
and they do it 'cause they know something you don't.
他还真是说得头头是道
He like this at home?
怎么 你觉得我会让她们住进来吗
You think I'd let'em live in my home?
笑吧 笑吧 一年后你们就笑不出来了
Laugh, laugh. You won't be laughing in a year.
当你们负担不起这里的消费的时候 你们就笑不出来了
When you won't be able to afford to live here.
她们搬进来 她们就会掌管这里
They move in, they take over.
她们会将那些无家可归者赶出公园
They kick the homeless out of the park
就好像那些无家可归者无权住在公园里一样
as if they don't have a God given right to sleep there.
我们就像史前的恐龙 朋友们
We are dinosaurs, my friend.
某颗巨大无比的彗星即将毁灭我们的家园
And a big, fat comet is headed for our sweet slice of earth.
而那颗彗星 就是那家星巴克
And that comet is a Starbucks.
他没要我出示身份证
Oh, he didn't card me.
-我一定看上去很性感 -你确实如此
- I must look hot. - You do.
我告诉过你的 你并不要打扮得像个妓女
And I told you, you don't need those whore shorts.
来吧 嗨起来
Come on, let's dance.
我尝试过了 萨米 我尝试过与你做朋友
I tried, Sammi. I've tried to be your friend.
因为你是弗兰克的女儿
Because you're Frank's daughter,
而弗兰克是我的丈夫
and Frank's my husband.
但我今天认识到 我是你的继母
But I realized today, I'm your step-mother.
所以为了能成为一个好继母
And so to be a good step-mother to you
就必须做到一个母亲的责任 而不是像朋友那样
is to be a parent to you rather than a friend.
所以 作为一个母亲 我有责任告诉你
So, as a parent, it's my responsibility
为什么人们都不喜欢你
to tell you that the reason people don't like you,
为什么你父亲也不想待在你身边
and that your father doesn't want to be around you,
是因为你真的 太贫穷 太懒惰了
is because you're very, very needy.
我只是觉得你应该知道这一点
I just think you should know that,
但你可以努力改善
and then you can work on it.
你贫穷 懒惰 烦人
You're needy and annoying.
还很骚 也不是个好母亲
And slutty, and a bad mother.
我觉得这应该是查克的
I think this belongs to Chuckie.
混蛋
Asshole.
哦 糟糕 快走 黛比 快走
Aw, shit. Come on, Debs, let's go!
-哦天啊 -你想以后再这么嗨
- Oh, my God. - You want to dress like that
在酒吧里狂舞的话 你就得拥有快速逃跑的技能
and hang in bars, you gotta learn to run faster.
刚才太疯狂了 我简直不敢相信你这么做了
That was insane, I can't believe you just did that.
我的个操
Holy shit.
他是怎么知道的
How'd he know?
发生什么了
What's going on?
告诉过了你们了
Told you.
啦啦啦啦
Arr-ar-ar-aroooo!